We are at the same point as when the
iPhone came out for crypto. The change
was that the iPhone came out to allow
Uber. For crypto, it's obvious. It's the
agents. It's plain and simple, the
agents. So, the fact that to me, the
ghost city analogy for Ghost Rails is
about you build all this infrastructure,
you build Ethereum, you build Bitcoin,
you develop this whole thing, people
know where it is. It needs time to
survive the test of [music] time. It
needs people looking at it and then it
can take off. What's going on guys?
Today we got a great conversation with
Jordi Visser. In this conversation, we
talk about what's going on with consumer
AI agents. How is it affecting financial
markets? Why are there certain stocks
that everyone's excited about? But
Jord's got some data that says that
they're actually under a lot of
pressure. Bitcoin broke out
consolidating. Is it going to go up? Is
it going to go down? Are we in a Bitcoin
bull market? And where else is value
going to acrew in your portfolio? What
are the assets you don't own that Jordy
thinks you should? All that much more in
this conversation with Jordy Visser. All
right, Jordy. Uh, crypto has done a very
good job of hanging in there all week
long, even though a number of other
things have come under pressure. Why do
you think crypto is trading so well?
>> When did we last see each other?
>> Couple days ago, a Tuesday. We We did a
drive by high five.
>> I walk into an event not [clears throat]
knowing you're there. I thought we were
friends. We do this. [laughter]
>> We walk through a turn style the other
way. See you. Oh, see you. How you
>> The difference between you and I is you
went for multiple days. See? Uh,
[laughter] young Paraguan. Listen, I'm a
expert at this. I took my train down to
DC, did my 15-minute talk and got right
back on the train and came back. You
stayed.
>> I stayed and had the best time. And for
the people who know that I had a great
time, you know who you are. I had a
great time. Um, okay. So, whenever you
The great thing about technical
analysis, we talked a lot about the
importance of the original break uh in
Bitcoin from the low60s up. But what was
important was the negative news that was
happening in the time before. Mhm.
>> Clarity goes down to close to 0%. Uh Fed
rate hikes are going through the roof in
terms of expectations and at the same
time you have the cold wallet incident
and yet Bitcoin stayed at like 60 to 65.
And so the second that anything good
happens. Oh, Bessant intervenes in the
yen and then we get all this debasement
stuff and it breaks out but it stays
under the important levels of kind of
the highs from the prior 6 months which
were right around 82. So now we gap up
again. So the question is when you're
doing these in technical analysis where
first you handle bad news. You go up
what happened when we broke out last
week? The Fed raised rates 10ear rates
are going higher. Equities are you know
breath is breaking down in the market
and yet we still found a way to go
higher again. So I believe based on the
inbound traffic I'm getting from
everybody. everyone but people that
manage trillions of dollars. So not the
analysts who work for him, the people
who manage trillions of dollars
asking me to talk about the paper I
wrote two months ago to explain why the
paper I wrote on tokenization will
change the world, what that means. So I
think we've entered a point where you
have to realize that
people are starting to ask questions
about it. Part of this is because of the
events that have occurred with consumer
agents and things where I've connected
the dots, but part of this is also what
happened last year. And I think there's
PTSD. People missed Micron. They missed
the semiconductor trade. And so I think
what's starting to happen here is they
know crypto is not dead, meaning they
kind of waved it off. So people that
manage lots of money that need to
produce alpha, this is not a greed
thing. I think there's FOMO starting to
set in. You think that there's FOMO
coming from Wall Street on the crypto
trade?
>> There's no doubt in my mind. Now, I said
on this show that I believe that 2027
would be the important year. And the
reason is this. You need to have FOMO
first because we're nearing the end of
the calendar year. And I'm spending a
lot of time like I did in DC about
machine time versus human time. Human
time moves really slow. Crypto doesn't
move slow. It moves very fast. AI
doesn't move slow. It moves very fast.
Oh, rates are going higher. or this is
going to hurt the housing market. This
is going to hurt small caps. I posted
something on X today. So, let me get
this straight. The Mag 7 are near
all-time high and the Russell 2000 is
breaking down, which means breath is
breaking down. And if you do a chart for
all of you breath fearmongers now of the
market, you'll realize that, oh, QQQ
over
IWM has been a trade since the iPhone
came into existence. If you're not part
of the digital economy, you're
suffering. So I think there's an element
that crypto now has a fundamental use.
It has public companies which means they
can do a little bit of investing.
They're not going into the tokens but
they are looking. But I think the fact
that you and I talk about all the time
and we have a lot of different
listeners. I write about the
relationship. I set up a business based
on the importance of AI to crypto
disrupting macro. I think FOMO is
kicking in because they're trying to
figure out ways to make money because
it's been kind of a frustrating year for
Alpha. And I'm just going to give you
one example because I can tell by people
reaching out on on me on things like
Visa and Mastercard. So Visa and
Mastercard are your classic examples of
things that oh crypto is not going to
disrupt them. And I'm just like of
course it will. Like I don't even know
how you could argue they're going to
benefit maybe initially but not in 5
years.
>> Why?
We're entering a deflationary period
that people just do not understand.
Deflation, not inflation. Deflation. You
and I agree on that. The deflationary
pressures that come from AI are intense.
It's just a matter of how long it takes
for it to filter through.
But where it's really going to filter
through is when people are having
agents, an agent's job is to find their
airline ticket for the cheapest price
that satisfies to book a travel thing
where they're stripping out the
middlemen as much as possible. Visa and
Mastercard by definition are middlemen.
So when people argue with me on this,
they go, "Well, no, no, they you need
this for this. They're going to
benefit." Blah, blah, blah. I'm like,
"Yeah, just like Salesforce.com, you see
Salesforce.com lately, it's up big. It's
down 10% this year. S&P's up 12. So it's
underperformed by 22%. Semiconductors,
my thematic portfolio is up 45%.
Salesforce down here. Even the Mag 7,
they're up 10%. They've underperformed.
I think people are making a mistake on
Vis and Mastercard. They're not going
out of business. But at some point, you
have to recognize that terminal value
matters again. And crypto and
tokenization are going to change the
world because it unleashes a lot of them
too because wealth becomes money. I
wrote about that this week. It's on
Substack. But on the other side, it
brings an enormous amount of
entrepreneurs that you can invest in
because they're going to have tokens. Is
it going to be this year? No. But it'll
be in five years. So where Visa and
Mastercard go, it's not about them going
out of business. It's about in five
years, will people still be paying a
vig? Agents won't. Agents don't pay
vigs. Agents figure out how. So people
tell me consumer behavior, they know
consumer behavior. I'm sorry, but you
don't know agent behavior. Agent
behavior is all about the goals. And the
goals are find things fast and cheap.
>> In the last bull market, there was a lot
of institutions that they started to dip
their toes. and dipping toes because
they're so big felt really big to the
crypto industry. So if you have, you
know, hundred billion dollars of assets
and you take 1%, it's a billion dollars.
In the crypto world, there was almost no
funds that had a billion dollars. And so
[clears throat] all of a sudden
quotequote smart money or the big guys
show up and they're wow, they put a
billion dollars.
>> To them, it was like uh let's see what
happens here. You know, it's a 1%
allocation.
I do feel like Wall Street, they're
ready for the fat pitch now. They last
cycle dipped their toe. They know what
this thing can do when it's going in the
right direction. They understand it's
super volatile. They're glad they just
dipped their toes and they didn't go all
in cuz they saw the volatility. But your
point about FOMO, it's like uh three
balls, two strikes, bottom of the ninth,
and you know the pitcher's going to
throw a fast ball and they're just
waiting. And I don't know when you
probably understand better than me like
what are the trigger that's going to let
them you know just swing but this time
it's not you know a billion it's 10 20
30 billion [clears throat] per firm it's
bitcoin other cryptos tokenization like
now they are ready to play this whole
thing and some of it is they have more
options now they couldn't just go buy
you know bitcoin before so they had to
wait for the ETFs y
>> but also how many public companies are
there now that give them some degree of
exposure to individual cryptos or
tokenization or even you know crypto
being used or blockchains being used in
certain verticals like the addressable
you know uh market of what they can
invest in has grown so much as well that
they actually can put more money to work
at the same time.
So, let's talk about um what you just
said and and let's go a fat pitch. Let's
go back to 2122 when they they stubbed
their toe, okay?
>> They bought at the highs, they jumped
into NFTts, they jumped into FTX, they
jumped into a whole bunch of things and
it seemed like an obvious situation.
Now, the reality is behind closed doors,
the VC world was pumping an enormous
amount of money into SAS businesses and
into crypto. Co is just over. We're in a
raging bull market. I've said this
before, I'll say it again. For crypto,
that was the.com bubble. Like,
everyone's looking for the.com bubble in
AI. That was the dot bubble for crypto.
It wasn't debt, [snorts]
but it was VC money that came in. Well,
a lot of these rails, they don't need VC
money now. So, with AI, the whole world
is changing. And this is part of my
thing. You don't need to hire people and
you get to use digital agents and go
through it. The thing that saved.com
bubble companies is in 2007 there was a
change that was able to use those rails.
And I keep saying this over and over
again. We were at the same point as when
the iPhone came out for crypto. The
change was that the iPhone came out to
allow Uber. I'll joke about this all the
time, but you can't take a laptop up and
be ordering a car outside. You need
Wi-Fi, cellular. You needed a smartphone
to be able to have Uber work.
>> Well, GPS in the phone was probably the
most important part. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You you you couldn't do it. So, we
needed an app store.
For crypto, it's obvious. It's the
agents. It's plain and simple, the
agents. So the fact that to me I've been
talking about this for a while that the
ghost city analogy for ghost rails is
about you build all this infrastructure,
you build Ethereum, you build Bitcoin,
you develop this whole thing. People
know where it is. It needs time to
survive the test of time. It needs
people looking at it and then it can
take off. Peter Lynch wrote a book that
he's still famous for which is all about
oneupping Wall Street. The beauty of
this is
Wall Street doesn't cover tokens and
crypto. They're starting to get involved
in the rails, but they don't cover
individual tokens. So, if you're at a
big mutual fund or a big pension fund,
you're like, you know what I'd really
like to see? Hey, can you get me the
Morgan Stanley research on on crypto
tokens? Doesn't exist. So, before when
you're in
>> TV research exists,
>> yes. Yes. I I And again,
>> Mr. Research exists.
>> It's live now. It's live. It went out
this week. And now every week I'll be
going through the vertical. So yes, that
was what I planned. My business was
about the fact that Peter Lynch's
philosophy was the best way to make
money is to be early on something, but
the only way to be early on something is
to know that the money is not invested
in the thing that you're early on and
Wall Street doesn't cover it. That was
his whole theory that was one uping Wall
Street. Well, that's where I believe we
are in crypto. So for all the people
have committed their time where they
understand every token that I put in my
46th name index, they already know what
they are. you have a huge advantage and
the money is enormous on the other side
because the beauty of the crypto
guardrails are the valuation is still $4
trillion compared to 900 trillion of
asset and all of those assets are going
to be tokenized and be on chain. Is it
going to happen tomorrow? No. But you
don't invest in things based on today.
You based on their growth. If you come
up with a great idea like Starbucks and
you have one store, you know how they
start to really get excited when you go
to two stores, three stores, four
stores. It's about growth at a very low
level. Everyone that screwed up the
token trade. I wrote a paper on
inference. We talked about Micron almost
all of last year.
The smartest people missed it. And they
missed it because they didn't understand
compute. This trade is still the same.
You want to be long compute speed. You
want to be long crypto speed. You want
to be short everything that has
friction. My presentation in DC was
about being long speed, short friction.
I was saying it to politicians. Ultimate
friction.
Why are senior people leaving Google?
Why hasn't Google been able to do what
Anthropic and OpenAI did? Why aren't
people asking that question that the
best AI models are not at companies
worth with the biggest balance sheets?
Anthropic went from 3 billion in
revenues to where it is today. Let's say
80. In the same amount of time, as I
said on stage, the Clarity Act went from
an idea to rejection. In the same amount
of time that Anthropic went up, you want
to be short friction. You want to be
long speed. And we're at that point now
where that is starting to play out. And
I think crypto guardrails and the whole
crypto system, you're going to have a
lot of people knocking on your doors and
this is going to be money that's coming
in. The problem is they don't have
access to it because these funds can't
invest in
these tokens at this point. That'll all
change over time, but what they can
invest in is Ethereum and Bitcoin and
then all of the stocks that are there. I
think you're going to see an evolution
that's going to change next year.
>> Today's episode is brought to you by
Arch Public. Arch public has just
expanded its agentic trading platform
beyond crypto. So pay attention. This is
a big one. Now they are automating
strategies across stocks, commodities,
and ETFs. And I think that this is going
to be huge. You can now automatically
take profits when one market hits new
all-time highs and rotate that capital
into other markets showing more
opportunity. Whether you're rotating
capital into AI stocks, gold, if you're
investing in the S&P 500, or you're
accumulating Bitcoin, Arch Public brings
real discipline and automation to your
investment strategy. Additionally,
they've launched a powerful new tax loss
harvesting tool. With crypto being so
volatile and its exemption from the wash
sale rule, Arch Public can offset gains
with losses without compromising your
long-term positions. It's exactly what
every serious investor does.
Institutional grade automation that
works across every major asset class.
[music] There's no more emotional
trading, no more missing tax
opportunities, just smarter, hands-free
execution of your preferred strategies.
Go to archpub.com
right now. Connect with their team. Set
up a time. Bring your accountant if
you'd like. Then you can learn what
automated trading can do for you.
archpub.com.
This whole idea of uh the AI agents, the
uh ability to use this technology, how
it goes faster, etc. I think a lot of
folks have focused on the intelligence
for raffle reasons is, you know, is it a
130, 140, 150 IQ? How do I get as much
of that as possible by going long
compute? Uh the more people that use the
intelligence, obviously, the more
productive they should become. All that
kind of stuff. But one aspect I don't
hear a lot of people talk about which I
catch myself now I try to be very
conscious of my consumer behaviors
its memory is better than me now and I
find myself telling various agents
remind me tomorrow to do something at
this time put this in your memory and
don't forget it make sure that whenever
you do this task you always remember to
do xyz and it hit me if this thing is
smarter than us and it has better memory
than us. What can it not do? like you
are going to just turn over all of this
stuff to it and everyone wants to talk
about intelligence but the memory
component when you start talking about
finance start talking about financial
data that feels like a huge piece of
this is whenever you talk to someone
smart in finance what do they know they
know history they could tell you
different cycles they could tell you
different you know a catalyst they could
tell you things that triggered sell-offs
all of the stuff and you're like wow
this person's really smart they
understand all this they are no match
for the memory of a financial agent
So th [clears throat] this is where we
start going from the reality of the
importance of enterprise agents and what
we just went through the last year to
consumer agents.
So let's separate memory into two
[clears throat] components. I ask chat
GPT uh about how to fix something in my
house. I ask it about some random thing
that happens. Those are things I don't
care about a memory of. And that's
pretty much what you dominate a chatbot
with with Muse and for you Instinct.
I use it for everything memory wise. So
like if I'm on a trip now, I can just
take a photo, upload it into Muse. Don't
have to say anything. I just have to go
back at some point and go, "Hey, just
take everything that I did on that trip,
all the receipts, and put it into a uh
into something for my company, for my
accountant." It's there. It has the
memory of everything. Hey, I booked a
trip to so- and so. Can you send me the
details of my trip to LA? And I just did
this with it this morning. It sends me
everything that I booked during the
time, the meetings I have, where I'm
staying, the whole thing. It asks me if
it wants me to put it any place. The me
the personal memory, the Jarvis, you
know, from Iron Man, it exists now. And
so those memories are really important,
but those only come with a consumer
agent where you're actually giving them
access to everything. So, I don't I just
don't think people have until they use a
consumer agent, they don't realize what
just happened. Now, to get back to your
IQ point last week, [snorts] I talked
about the point in situational awareness
on page 71 where it goes parabolic. So
when you watch your children grow up,
like your kids are young,
>> their IQ is not real high at this point
in terms of
>> I know [laughter]
>> my my son still is got a hard time
sometimes slowing himself down. So he
just runs into the wall as the stopping
point.
>> And you told me he would try to be
Superman. Like literally tried to be see
if see if he was Superman. Okay.
>> Oh, he Yeah.
>> Yeah. And it didn't work. Okay.
>> A nice scar on his face for a while.
[laughter]
>> So here here's the thing. At some point
the intelligence gets to the point where
the kids are really smart and they're
smarter than you, but it takes
>> where we're starting from. There's
there's only [laughter] up to
>> but no matter what it's it's a
progression and it keeps going with the
AI models reaching the point so much has
happened in the last 3 months, two and a
half months. And I'm going to say two
and a half and I'm going to uh preview
something that I'm going to do in my
video this weekend. I [snorts] think
what doesn't get talked about enough
with Muse
Meadow was left for dead in June and on
July 2nd it he had a town hall meeting
or there was a report of a town hall
meeting. Do you remember this?
>> Yeah.
>> And and he said the progress on what we
found out later it said AI and like all
the media but it was really their
internal work on agents was not going at
the pace they expected.
>> How do you go from that point to Muse in
two months?
>> You want me to tell you how? I'll give
you tell me how and then I'll tell you
the facts.
>> I heard that uh he moved his desk over
to the Meta AI team and he sat there and
I've seen him do it before. You know, he
just wore rooms, all stuff, whatever.
>> How do you, if you're on that team, not
figure it out when the big boss says,
"Hey, this is important."
>> It was from applying pressure. Okay.
Yeah. What do you think?
>> Well, I'm going to show exactly what
happened. Now, when I say exactly, I
just want to make sure people know if
you haven't done this before.
Ask your LLM to say, "Hey, I want to
figure out how we could go from this
point to this point, and I want you to
go through every public
announcement by any employee that worked
in that group there, whether it's a in
Reddit, wherever it is." And then it
puts together a timeline of the changes.
A week after that news story came out,
there was a breakthrough. So the reason
this is important is whatever caused it,
they started releasing new versions of
Muse
>> consistently just like Anthropic does.
Like you could see they were making
progress cuz each one they were cuz they
were under pressure. This [snorts] is
the reason why with this consumer agent
point with Instinct and with Meta, you
don't think OpenAI is now racing to get
their agent out because they don't want
to lose the eyeball battle.
>> So right now Meta has this advantage,
but we're going to start getting
consumer
consumer agent releases, personal
assistance from everyone now.
>> And so so what does a user do? Do they
adopt all of them? Do they just pick one
they like? How do they navigate this uh
onslaught of everyone wants them to use
their agent? This is where I I'm already
locked into Muse. I It's I I my own
experience is unlike an LLM, I've always
used Chat GPT the most except for one
little window when Claude Code went
through it, but then I went right back
to Chat GPT
and I'm still I I like Astra better than
than than But then again, we had two new
releases this week. Opus 5.5 is just
ridiculous. Um, but Muse, it's locked in
because it has all my information now
and it's doing all this work. It's
connected to my emails. It's doing
everything I want and I'm getting used
to it and it's very hard for me to see
that I would change it cuz I haven't run
into anything yet where it made a
mistake or did something wrong. It's
really, really amazing. The reason I
bring it up is as you're going through
this thing and you're thinking about the
importance of agents, you have to get
back to the situational awareness thing.
We're at a point where so much
incredible stuff is happening and the
media focuses on oh my god there was a
hacking but at the same time we're
making advancements with Navier Stokes
and then Anthropic comes out with
something on crisper.
If you go through X, you'll get 50% of
biologists and people saying, "This is
BS. They're just releasing this for the
IPO." And then I'm going, "Well, the
only one I care about is the guy who is
in Code Breaker,
>> who is from MIT, who's one of the two
renowned people in Crisper that said,
"This is amazing. This is a
breakthrough." Like, you're never going
to get anything where it's signal. It's
always going to be noise. There's always
going to be half the population says
it's not there. And that's just human
beings. But where is no doubt that for
the next 12 months, if you want to make
money, you're going to have to make it
on compute and on the guard rails for
these agents because how many deals did
Muse do this week with Shopify,
Instacart, like it's just growing.
PayPal, everything is happening. So, I
think this is the critical point where
the IQ has reached a level where we're
at recursive self-improvement and every
month is going to be another month of
just advancements.
>> What happens when Muse gets blocked by
Amazon? which I think just happened and
you want to use one. It has all your
information, but a very key use case for
that agent gets cut off, not because
they made a mistake or anything, but
because a competitor is trying to
introduce that friction, reduce speed.
>> Mh.
>> Do you then have to go and adopt
Amazon's agent? Or do you think it's a
world where your Muse agent will then
talk to an Amazon agent and that
communication would be the same thing as
you as a human going to the website, but
now they're just going to create their
own agent and agent to agent
communication. I again I I think the
issue is going to come you can't stop
this like I I think when um Android came
out verse Apple and you're trying to
figure out can you use Uber on Android
eventually or could I mean I think the
friction they'll try to do whatever they
can I think Amazon and they're all
competing but in the end I don't see how
to go will instinct be allowed to use
all of them I mean I I I just don't see
if Amazon wants to lose business because
everyone's on Muse and everyone starts
using Shopify or starts using Instacart
instead of Amazon, then it'll just drive
markets other places. So, it's not that
they're going to end these things. I
think in the end, uh they've got
shareholders and if they take a
decision, then it's like, okay, we're
going to we're going to enter our own
one and because we have the Amazon
world, we're going to dominate. And then
you've got Apple and Apple's going to
have Siri. They're all I mean, this is
going to be like a growing uh agentic
side. I just don't see how they can
block things off because then they're
choosing silos and they're limiting the
ability of controlling a lot of it and I
just don't see how this is going to be
anything more than the initial days and
how they're dealing with this. I think
in the end it's just going to be divvied
up.
>> It's fascinating to think about Black
Rockck. They came out with a paper this
week talking about AI and um crypto.
Thank you for listening to the podcast
the last [laughter] six months. Um I I
thought that it was fantastically uh
written or very well done. Um
>> I would say 90% of it is very similar
things that you've been talking about.
Uh there is 10 or 15% though in there
that I think they kind of have different
viewpoints and some of it maybe because
they're coming from more of a financial
mindset and a traditional finance. Um
but what I think people look back on the
Bitcoin ETFs, the ETF was important, but
the ETF really only happened once Uncle
Larry said, "I'm ready to do an ETF."
And then somehow it all got approved.
>> Black Rockck writing the paper, there's
a lot of papers that have been written
about Bitcoin or crypto and AI.
>> Y,
>> but Black Rockck writing it again kind
of is like, oh, okay, the adults in the
room also agree now. Now it is for real.
It feels like a contrarian viewpoint
that just literally with the release of
one paper goes from contrarian to
consensus. Do you agree?
>> Um, yeah. I think there was a targeted
reason for the release though too based
on the fact that in the same week they
also put three funds on chain. So
>> Oh, they have an agenda.
>> Yeah. Well, yeah, an agenda is the
right. They have a business and I think
they're selling what they're doing and
they're ahead of
>> the banks. Yeah.
>> So, uh they're trying to stay ahead on
this just like Amazon's trying to not
fall behind to Meta and Open AI. I mean,
at the end of the day, the speed of
change is going so rapidly and inside
these walls, you have a lot to lose. So,
on the flip side, when whenever I use
Michael Sailor's line of [snorts] you
don't find Bitcoin, Bitcoin finds you,
which is a reference to the fact that
until you actually need Bitcoin, you're
not going to care. I think the same
thing happens with AI. I think every
time something happens in artificial
intelligence, there's a fear of the SAS
apocalypse in in in your name or
whatever. And we see this time and time
again where something will fall 30, 40,
50%. A lot of the software names have
not come back. And like I said with
Salesforce, Salesforce has bounced, but
it's still down 10% year-to- date and
it's down 15% over the last 5 years. Um,
is that good? That's that's not
something you want to invest in. Um, and
again, Bitcoin is down significantly
from the highs. So, you can make the
argument if you just pick this cherry
pick this this point of time. Um, I I I
think this is going to be a
disruptionfilled point and I think
everyone's trying to get the jump on
anyone. BlackRock has a huge advantage
as some place that people trust from a
asset manager perspective that has
already made this big commitment to
crypto, but they don't. I mean,
Fidelity's there, Franklin Templeton's
there. It's not like they're the only
ones. Uh I think the entire side is
trying to drive the Morgan Stanley's,
the Bank Americans, the Goldman Sachs to
make sure that they're focused on it and
they didn't really get focused on it
honestly until what the last year maybe
the last it's been this year that they
were kind of forced into it. So there is
a fear of missing out and that's the
other part of the FOMO when you really
look and you don't think about the
charts or you don't think about anything
like what's happened this year in
crypto.
A lot's gone on. I know people don't
like the word crypto. It's amazing to
me. I like I like provoking uh anger in
people. They were digital assets.
I was talking to someone yesterday who
you had on who you connected us with who
I brought up NFTTS like what's a bad
word. Yeah, I get it. What do you want
to call it? I was like digital assets.
Everything's a digital asset now. It's
acceptable. So, I think the whole
industry is in a chase mode and I just
think Black Rockck has the biggest
audience and the easiest time to do this
stuff. Today's episode is brought to you
by Galaxy 1. A lot of people got their
money working for them, but the question
now, how hard is it working? Well, the
folks over at Galaxy 1, they're taking a
very different approach. [music]
Everyone earns 3.5% APY using Galaxy 1
Cash. And if you make over $200,000 a
year, that means you're probably an
accredited investor. And then you can
earn up to 8% on your cash guaranteed by
Galaxy Digital. The best part though is
that you can actually set it so that
your yield immediately is reinvested
into your favorite stocks, crypto, or
ETFs. You don't got to think about it
every single month. It just
automatically does it for you. That's
why I love Galaxy 1. So, if your cash
isn't working as hard as you are, then
it's time to make a move. Check out the
link in the description and start
earning today. Today's episode is
brought to you by Uphold. Are you
someone who's tired of juggling multiple
apps just to trade, earn, stake, or
spend your crypto? Then listen up
because Uphold does all of that in one
single unified platform. You can access
300 plus crypto and fiat currencies with
an interface that works for you whether
you're a beginner or an expert. Uphold
also [music] features any to any swaps
where you can swap crypto to fiat, fiat
to metals, and tokens to tokens directly
in the app. If you prefer self-custody,
Uphold's vault gives you multi-stick
security, key recovery, direct trading
access, and peace of mind without giving
up convenience. Uphold is also 100%
reserved, meaning no fractional
practices and proof of reserves are
updated every 30 seconds, so you can
verify your assets anytime. For US
users, you can even earn yield on
dollars with the USD interest account.
No fees, no minimums, and funds are
insured up to $2.5 million through the
Atomic Cash Suite program. If you want
one app for your entire digital asset
life, check out Uphold today. Go to
uphold.com to learn more. Uphold.com.
[music] Go check them out today. Last
week we talked a lot about the agents
and uh a number of things that now I
think are moving rapidly in a matter of
weeks from contrarian to consensus. Uh
on Monday, Meta gapped up almost 15% or
so. Uh I don't know if we get a pat on
the back. Maybe we get like a little
golf clap, right? Um what is your
thought process on like okay, we know
the consumer agents are going to become
a thing. People are already adopting
them. You and I are adopting them. We're
using them very aggressively. What does
that mean for the companies? Black
Rockck's talking about this. Meta's
building this. Like, do all of these
companies actually see it flow through
to performance and ultimately higher
stock prices, or is there maybe a period
of time where there's tons of adoption,
but stock prices don't really reflect
that until they can show that they can
actually monetize these services?
I think the market on Monday uh set a
very similar framework to what happened
with semiconductors saying oh my god the
agent world started today how do we make
money off agents
I think the disappointment will come and
again how you measure the monetary
benefits to Meta well now they get the
benefit of the doubt because they have
this growth engine so if you can find
anything positive in there it offsets
the debt that they've been taking the
fact that the Mag 7 broke to all-time
highs on the same day. And last week I
did talk about the fact and I did on my
my my weekend show that the Mag 7 all
benefit from the agentic side in some
way. I mean Amazon has Alexa, Apple has
Siri, Google has Gemini. Like they're
all ways that you're going to benefit on
this by having a personal assistant. I
mean for Muse, imagine if Google said,
"I'm not you can't access my
my account." I I it would it would be
very very difficult to to go through.
Now Muse can absolutely help me with
Amazon because they just sign in under
my name and go through it. And that's
the beauty of like, well, how do you
know it's not me? You can't buy things
then. Okay, great. But can you do the
research and tell me what I should look
for and go through it? That is one of
the powers of Muse, by the way. people
haven't used it. If you're taking a trip
and you want to go find restaurants in a
city, one of the things I hate the most
about the way search works is when you
type that in, you get whatever papers
and advertisers have been paid to do
that. When you use Muse, you you you
>> get the answer.
>> You get the answer. Um, so I I think the
the marketing
>> You're saying Muse is a filter?
>> Uh, to a to a degree. That's it's it's
it's really hurting. I I don't
understand still the advertising side.
So I don't understand this whole thing
of people being excited about ads
personally. I just
>> ads in inmuse
>> like anything regarding ads. When I hear
consumer agents
I I'm thinking that agents will be
making decisions with no preferences. I
don't know why people don't understand
this. Like human beings
McDonald's putting a a photo of a
burger. No offense to anyone listening
from McDonald's but I don't eat
McDonald's. And so when I see a photo I
know and they try to make it look good.
>> It's best restaurant in America.
>> It definitely controls a lot of the food
supply in the country. Um
>> based
what is an AI agent going to make
decisions on? They're going to make them
based on price, reviews, all of these
different things, but it's not going to
be based on advertising. So maybe that's
not today, but eventually it is. So when
I hear people talk about consumer
behavior, I think the agent side is
still going to be compute. So for
everyone who's like worried about
semiconductors and stuff, watch this
Sunday when I show you where we are. The
compute needs just went up
exponentially.
Remember Meta has built a huge data
center in in in Louisiana. Why?
They're not selling the compute.
Remember that was the story back in
June. Also, they didn't sell any.
They're not doing what they actually
have a need for it. Why do they have a
need for it? because of their consumer
agents and at some point this week there
was a weight list where you couldn't get
on just like it was for Instinct. So I
think consumer agents is going to lead
to enormous amount of compute. I do
think there'll be a buzz trade for MAG 7
and things like that. I don't think
they're going to outperform the S&P. I
think they'll [snorts] outperform small
caps as people get panicked because of
rates and because of oil. But in the end
I do think that you can make money off
this. But I think the place where you
want to go and what are the agents
using? They're using crypto. What do
they need? They need compute. Those are
the trades. Are you telling me that
there's going to be zero ability to
create like a cute agent that can flirt
with somebody else's agent to get a
sale? That's not going to be a thing.
>> It's not going to be a thing.
>> All right. Well, there's some businesses
that going to be in trouble there. Um,
when you think through everything that's
happening in the product side, one
aspect that I think people are starting
to almost forget about is there's a huge
technical side to this. And Mused, I
think the beauty of it is like you have
no clue what model they're using. You
have no clue how much to compute costs.
You don't know a token. The average
person's never even heard that term,
right? All they know is there's a piece
of software that is a product. I tell it
to do something, it does it. It's magic.
>> On the technical side, uh, recently
Doresh sat down with Nome Brown and, uh,
it was pretty interesting conversation.
What were your main takeaways?
Uh I
lately my AI listening on podcast has
gone down.
>> Okay. Interesting.
>> And the reason is
someone who we both know asked me this
yesterday because uh they're at the
moonshots uh event and I sat back and I
said here's the deal. When things are
changing so fast,
it's almost useless to listen to what
happened in the prior week because the
next week there's a whole new thing. So
unless it's something that's like
earthshattering like Opus 5.5 releasing
doesn't change anything. Chat GPT6 and
Soul Luna doesn't change anything.
>> I literally don't even think most people
>> care anymore when these new things
unless it is a huge step function
change.
>> Exactly. the iterative nobody
>> it does it it doesn't matter and Astra I
said it to people I I'm not going to
care anymore this thing is so good that
it does everything that I needed to do
which wasn't the case before and so the
time between them so that's the reason
>> one aspect of this I think is very
interesting is when we look at uh
measurements inside of Sylvia and we're
measuring let's say uh accuracy or uh
efficacy on certain benchmarks
we continue to talk internally without
an
Let's say that Opus scores 88 and the
Sylvia model scores 91 and let's say
maybe chat GBT whatever version scores
86.
Can a human tell the difference between
86 88 and 91? Probably not.
>> Yeah.
>> Can a human tell the difference between
40 and 90? Absolutely.
>> Yeah. But one of the questions is like
what is the the band of the human eye
cannot you know identify the difference
and I think that what you're talking
about in these new model releases
they're within the band of to the user
it's the same thing.
>> Y
>> and what you need is you need these
breakouts people only care when it is
obvious to them.
>> So before I I I go through what I am
listening to and and why this has
changed and the nome brown situation.
So, there was one that came out this
week, a benchmark that um Astra I think
got 100% and and and
Fable got 45.
>> Oo. This was a driving benchmark. So, it
was a driving from what I saw
simulation.
>> Okay.
>> And so, they had to learn
>> a fake test for a fake action
>> of course. Yeah. and they had to do it
and Astra ended up being able to do it
on like the second try and I'm not sure
that uh Fable finished the course. The
reason I bring that up is not to say
well this one's better than this. It's
to say that we're getting into the point
now where humanoids robotics full
self-driving become something important.
Remember um making snap decisions at a
given point and having the vision to
incorporate that and learning as you go
along it's going to take an enormous
amount of compute. So this is the
beginning of showing how the models are
now entering next stage. It's funny how
many people go. The images you have on
these slides on the weekend are so good.
Where do you do them? You guys don't
know how to do them. So again, I used to
use nano banana a long time ago. That
stopped. I remember
>> and and it has been chatbt since then.
But it's amazing to me that people don't
use them. I I mean I use it all day long
because I'm a visual learner. I prefer
it that way. All right. The gnome brown
thing because I think it's really
important
>> from open AI. Yes, from Anome Brown from
OpenAI sat down with Dwar
there. There will be points if people
listen to it because Dwar is so he can
talk to an open AI researcher. So, one
of the smartest AI reachers in the
researchers in the world, he can speak
to him at eye to eye level and talk
about things. You're like, I don't
understand what that means. I'm the
same. Like, there's certain things I'm
like, skip to the part I care about. So,
there's two parts that are really
important. So I think what I'm really
good at is consuming a lot of
information and then picking out the two
or three things that are I want to
double click on. And there were two
things in there based on the traffic
coming to me. One was the hugging face
thing which no one Brown is a big part
of and he talked about it. You go in
there and he made this phrase the most
important line in the entire thing. We
underestimated
the capabilities of AI.
>> We won't Yeah. And we won't
underestimate it again. I think every
parent goes through that. So I want to
make sure you have that analogy.
At some point you underestimate your
child's ability to do something that you
were taking for granted. So I think for
people who are scared of oh these things
are rogue and they're going to go over.
No, it was the humans underestimating.
It's the most important line in there in
terms of okay on the second part they
spent a lot of time on where the model
is now. and they talked about Navier
Stokes and that is a really important
thing. That's where Muse fits in. We've
entered in the last two months a very
important point and it gets back to he
admitted we're in that parabolic side of
situational awareness. He said it the as
as important as the agents are working
together and he describes how they work
together. It's unbelievable.
It is the model itself that has reached
the levels of being able to solve the
problems. So we are at a point of time
where breakthroughs are going to be
coming that are going to blow your mind.
Number one, that is not a time to be
bearish on stocks, [snorts] science
breakthroughs, cancer curing, stuff like
that. We're going to be having
breakthrough after breakthrough after
breakthrough. That's why the anthropic
news combined with this. So if you're
looking at the hugging face thing going,
"The world's going to end." It could.
And I've heard people describe how it
could happen. And I can I actually can
get to the point that if you combine
humanoids and they're on the planet and
rogue people, whatever, I can get there.
It's not going to happen. But I think
the more important thing is the
capabilities of it have reached a level
that the productivity, if you look at
that situational awareness thing, it's
going to go through the roof.
>> One more statement on this because I
said this down in DC. I've actually
reached a point of of thinking it is it
is just as wrong for people to say
everyone's going to lose their jobs,
okay, as the other side, which is to be
naive enough to then tell the same
people those they're just scaring you.
Nobody's going to lose their job. We're
going to create more jobs. That also is
not being honest cuz that sets you up
say I don't have to do anything. You
know what the right message is for
everyone listening? If you're older and
you're near retirement and you don't
care about your job,
>> okay, fine.
>> Yeah.
>> For your kids though, they need to use
AI. End of story. Like, if you're not
embracing AI, if you're not thinking, if
you're you get smarter, you whatever
everyone thinks of me, I spend a lot of
time trying to use AI to get smarter, to
use AI to build things, to use AI. I'm a
builder. I like to do it. This is going
to be an age of entrepreneurship, which
means you're going to have freedom. You
don't have to work for someone. Work,
job are bad words in my opinion. I don't
know why people want them. They want
them for identity. I get that. Smith
viser means fisherman. I get it. That's
what our lives have been about. But
don't you want to work for yourself and
don't you want to make money and don't
you want to go through it? I believe
investing and letting your money
compound at the same time as finding
ways to drive income is what it is. It's
not about working for someone. It's
about how do I make income and turn that
into more money. The people who are the
wealthiest on the planet, they don't get
paid a big b paycheck. Their money they
turned into more money. That's your
story. That's my story. I turned money
into more money by investing it and
going through it. And I think if
everyone just focuses, and that's why I
try to preach on the videos, learn AI,
understand the markets, understand
crypto, and you're going to be ahead of
the game from the people that control
most of the world's money. And that's
the way you make money is being in front
of the people. Back to the Peter Lynch
story. Bitcoin has hung in there where
we started this conversation. It is now
seems to be consolidating around 83 to
$87,000.
Is that a consolidation before a dump
back down into the 70s? Is that a
consolidation that then should lead to
another breakout? How do you think about
Bitcoin over the next six months?
Well, as I've been saying, I the reason
I wanted to create an index is to
separate what's happening in Bitcoin
from the ecosystem because I think the
ecosystem should be benefiting from the
agentic side and Bitcoin should be uh
benefiting from the ecosystem
benefiting. Uh I don't believe in the so
at some point in innovation
you go from liquidity to fundamentals
and I believe we're at the fundamental
stage now. Bitcoin doesn't fit in that
fundamental argument. Um, it's really
more for, hey, we're going to have a lot
more developers showing up here. We're
going to start building lots of things
because Robin Hood chain is driving.
Like, it's all these different
components that are getting people
excited about the fundamentals. And if
I'm right, what should be happening is
what's happening, which is tenure rates
have now gone higher by almost 100 basis
points.
And I think for the quarter, let's
assume it's up 60 70 basis points for
the quarter. The quarter is coming to an
end soon. And Bitcoin's up 60% for the
quarter with rates with tenure rates
going higher.
>> Is that good?
>> Yeah, that's good. And gold's not going
higher. This is not a liquidity
debasement trade. This is a fundamental
trade. So, uh, the fact that this
morning Salana was trading at 121 and
was up another 4% and it's moving in a
different way. I think these are all
signs
that money is looking into the space and
they're like, "Hey, this thing is
trading more volume." where RWA is going
to fit in. What's the growth rate of
this? Let me look at Hyperlquid. I just
think people are UN or they're doing the
homework. And that's why I said the
homework is happening at the end of this
year, which will be investments for next
year, but it's going to show up after we
get through the midterms. So, I don't
know when we're going to start kind of
the the the rally in stocks that allows
this to continue. It could happen in
December. It could happen before the
midterms and then go sideways. Uh, but I
definitely think as the MAG7 broke out
to new highs this week and as people are
worried about breath and they're worried
about all these things, the amount of
Google trend stock market crash,
everyone go look at it. Go look at the
last week
up to the highs of the year got to 100%.
So, as far as I'm concerned, people are
worried about something going on because
they're seeing all these things on
breath. They're seeing oil going higher.
They're seeing rates go higher. And I
said it in DC. I don't know if I said it
on this show, but I'll say it again. I
was in China in 2008 in May
just months before Lehman Brothers
collapsed.
Oil was at 155.
Here we are now 18 years later.
Oil is 100 and it's not even 100, but
let's just say 100.
155 verse 100. So it's down. You know
how much household net worth has gone
up? You know how much the economy has
gone up? You know how much disposable
income has gone higher? How can oil
matter in the long term? Can it freak
people out? Yeah. But if you're
listening to people my age or higher
telling you that oil matters and they're
giving you 1970 stuff just like they
told you about tariffs from Smoot Holly
and all the other things that have gone
on and they bring out all of these time
periods. These are just people that
don't need to be bullish. That's the end
story. They want to be bearish because
they're not making money in this period
because they believe that the world's
going to end from the death of the 40
trillion. And as I wrote in my token
tokenization paper this week, there's
195 trillion in the US net, not gross,
net. So take out the debt for
households. 95 trillion as of June and
40 trillion of debt. We're worried about
the 40 trillion when the households have
195 trillion. Tokenization
will turn that 195 trillion into
liquidity. That's going to happen over
the next 5 years. So, you can doubt it.
You can say Jord's crazy. Just go look
up tokenization and what's happening and
go read the Black Rockck Black Rockck
report. That's a lot of money that goes
to liquidity. We never need to print
again.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, we're not going to
die. I promise the world is going to be
better in the future than it is in the
past. The doomers are wrong. Jordi is
here. I appreciate you watching. Go
check him out. Jordy Visser on YouTube.
Go subscribe at 22V Research. And I
promise if you use AI, your life will
improve. See you next time.